Here are the instructions to manually implement the changes:
1. Add CSS link in the head section of index.html:
<link rel=\
stylesheet\ href=\css/blog_styles.css\>
2. Add this CSS code to css/blog_styles.css:
3. Add this HTML after the connect section in the first column:
See the CSS code in file: css/blog_styles_code.txt
See the blog HTML code in file: blog_html.txt
See the tools radar HTML code in file: tools_radar_html.txt
